ooshirts.com 2016-06-27

# ooShirts Privacy Policy

Effective as of January 12, 2012 

## 1\. Introduction

We take the privacy of our ooShirts customers very seriously. Please read this Privacy Policy to learn more about how ooShirts Inc. ("ooShirts," "we," our," or "us"), treats information, including personally identifiable information, in connection with the [http://ooshirts.com](http://www.ooshirts.com/) website (collectively the "ooShirts Service" or the "Service"). We provide this Privacy Policy because you have a right to know what information we collect, how it is protected and used, and the circumstances under which it may be disclosed. If you have comments, suggestions, questions, or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please contact us via email at [privacy@ooshirts.com](mailto:privacy@ooshirts.com) or in writing at: 64 Shattuck Square, #285, Berkeley, California 94704.

 _Online Privacy Standards._

We follow the principles supported by the Federal Trade Commission's Fair Information Practices Principles, currently available at <http://www.ftc.gov/reports/privacy3/fairinfo.shtm>.

 _What This Policy Covers._

This policy covers the ways in which ooShirts treats information, including personally identifiable information, which we obtain when you use our Service. We regard personally identifiable information as information that someone can use to identify or contact you in person, such as your real name, telephone number, email address, or physical mailing address. Information that we generate and use internally to identify you as a customer in our system (e.g., your order number) is not considered personally identifiable information. Your IP address is not considered personally identifiable information.

 _What This Policy Does Not Cover._

This policy does not cover the privacy practices of third parties that we do not own or control, such as the practices of third-party payment processing services or our partners and advertisers. In addition, we may provide links to other services and on occasion to other sites that may interest you. All of these sites operate independently of ooShirts and they have their own privacy and security practices. For your best online experience, we encourage you to review their policies before submitting any personal information to them. 

## 2\. How We Collect Information

**Information You Provide During Design Creation And Ordering**

When you create a design and order goods using the Service, we require that you provide your name, phone number, email address, your website URL (if applicable), and appropriate shipping and billing information for your order. We do not collect, nor do we store any other personally identifiable information for any customer.

**Information You Provide When Submitting A Rating Or Review**

After placing your order with ooShirts, you will have the opportunity to rate and review your order at the http://www.ooshirts.com website. When reviewing your order, we will ask that you provide your first name, last name, and the city and state in which you live. You will also have the option of uploading a photo with your review.

**Information We Do Not Collect From Any Users**

 _Children._

As explained further in our Terms of Use (available at <http://www.ooshirts.com/agreement>), you must be 18 years of age or older – or, if you are under the age of majority in your jurisdiction, have the consent of your parent or guardian – to use the ooShirts Service. Therefore, we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information about children. In accordance with Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), ooShirts will never knowingly solicit, nor will we accept, personally identifiable information from customers known to be under thirteen (13) years of age. If you believe that we have information from or about anyone under 13 years of age, please notify us by email at [privacy@ooshirts.com](mailto:privacy@ooshirts.com) or write to our Privacy Officer at the address noted above.

 _Social Security Number._

We do not require your social security number to use the ooShirts Service or to access any part of our site. ooShirts will 

_never_

ask for your social security number.

 _Payment Information._

The ooShirts Service makes it quick and convenient for you to make purchases using a third party payment processing service. When you make such a payment, ooShirts will not receive any additional personally identifiable information as a result of these transactions. Third-party payment providers operate independently of ooShirts, and we encourage our customers to fully review the Terms of Use and Privacy Policies of any such service used online.

**Information We Track**

 _Log Files._

Similar to many websites and internet services, we gather certain anonymous, non-personal information automatically and store it in web server log files. This information includes internet protocol addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), site entry/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click stream data. We use this information to improve our site, analyze trends, administer the site, and gather aggregate information about our member base as a whole. Aggregate information is data we collect about a group or category of services or members from which individual member identities have been removed, and therefore does not include your personally identifiable information.

 _Cookies._

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a member's computer for record-keeping purposes. It can also help us understand how our site visitors click to our site, what pages they view during their visit, and their account and preference information as members of the Service. Similar to many websites, the ooShirts Service stores a cookie on your computer. Cookies also allow us to track and understand the interests of our members in the aggregate, to enhance the overall experience on our site. Cookies used by ooShirts do not include your personally identifiable information.

If you prefer not to receive cookies, you can set your web browser software to disable them. To do so, please refer to the help section of your specific browser for more information on how to manage or disable cookies. 

## 3\. How We Use Information

**To Provide You With The ooShirts Service**

We use your information, including personally identifiable information, for the purposes of providing you with the Service, and with any ooShirts goods you may elect to order using the Service. We share your information, including your personally identifiable information, to the minimum extent necessary to accomplish this purpose. For example, if you elect to have goods shipped to you, we will share your name and shipping address with our distribution partners.

**In ooShirts Communications**

We use emails and/or prominent notifications on our website as our primary means to inform our members of important Service and promotional announcements.

 _Service-Related Announcements._

When you place an order at [http://ooshirts.com](http://www.ooshirts.com/), we use the email address provided during order placement to deliver important Service-related communications to you. These Service-related communications are considered a fundamental part the ooShirts Service, and you cannot opt-out of these email communications.

**On Our Website**

 _Site Statistics._

As noted above, we use information collected from our web log files to calculate and publish anonymous, non-personal, aggregate statistics that we believe our visitors are interested in viewing. For example, we may track and publish the total number of customers who have ordered a specific shirt color or style. We publish this data in aggregate form only, and do not publish any personally identifiable information in connection with this use.

 _Ratings and Reviews._

If you choose to rate or review your order at [http://www.ooshirts.com](http://www.ooshirts.com/), the information you provide during the rating and review process (e.g., your first name, last name, city, state, and any photo you upload) will be posted online alongside your rating or review. For an example of these ratings and reviews, please see <http://www.ooshirts.com/testimonials>. If you do not want your personally identifiable information to appear online in this context, please do not provide us with any such information during the rating and review process.

**For Internal Reporting and Analysis**

As noted above, we use information gathered from log files and cookies to improve our site, analyze trends, administer the site, track visitors' movements around the site, and to gather aggregate information about our visitors and customers as a whole. This data does not include your personally identifiable information. 

## 4\. How We Share and Disclose Information

**With Third Parties**

 _Sharing, Renting, and Selling Information We Collect._

We will neither rent nor sell your personally identifiable information to anyone. Occasionally we share anonymous, non-personal, aggregate information about our user base with partners or advertisers, and we may publish these aggregate usage statistics on our website for the interest of our visitors and customers. This shared or published data does not include the personally identifiable information of any person.

 _To Provide You With The ooShirts Service._

We share your information, including your personally identifiable information for the purpose of providing you with the ooShirts service, and any goods you may order through the Service. For example, if we ship you a shirt we will provide our shipping partners with your name and address.

 _Linked Services._

In some cases, we allow you to access or link to other web services through our website. For example, we allow members to share content using Facebook and Twitter, among others. We also allow you to pay for goods purchased through the Service using our selected third party payment processing provider. We make it easy for you to determine when you are accessing or linking to these other web services through our website. In all of these cases, those sites may choose to collect your personal information as they deem appropriate. As noted above, we are not responsible for or in control of how third parties collect, use, or disclose your information obtained through these linked services. We encourage you to be aware when you are using these third party services and, for your best online experience, we encourage you to review their policies before submitting any personal information to them.

**As Necessary In Certain Legal Circumstances**

 _Legal Requirements._

We reserve the right to disclose your information, including personally identifiable information, when we have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is necessary to (a) comply with any law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce these Terms of Use, including investigation of potential violations of these Terms of Use, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of ooShirts, its visitors or customers, or the public as required or permitted by law.

 _Acquisition._

If ooShirts becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, including bankruptcy, our assets, including visitor and customer information, may be transferred to a third party. At that time, your information may become subject to that third party's privacy policy. Before we transfer information, we will notify you either by email or by posting a prominent notice on our site, and we will remind you of your ability to add, edit or delete your personally identifiable information in advance of any such transfer. 

## 5\. How We Keep Information Secure

_Network Security._

Our partners employ a variety of commercially standard encryption and security technologies and procedures to protect information, including your personal information, from unauthorized access. Please be aware that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, thus, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

 _Management Procedures._

Our partners maintain standard physical and electronic procedural safeguards that limit access to your personally identifiable information to employees (or people working on our behalf and under confidentiality agreements) who, through the course of standard business activities, need to access your personally identifiable information. 

## 6\. Your Personal Choices

_Receiving Communications._

If you subscribe to any optional promotional communications, you will be able to unsubscribe from these communications through the emails we send you.

 _Deleting Your Information._

To completely delete any personal information we may have regarding you, please contact us at help@ooshirts.com. 

## 7\. Updates to Our Privacy Policy

From time to time, we will review and may make changes to our privacy policy. When we do so, we will notify you either by email or place a notice on our website. The most recent version of our privacy policy is always available from a link on our homepage, and at [http://ooshirts.com/privacy](http://www.ooshirts.com/privacy).
